<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASQ - Aspring for Quality</title>
    <link>/vi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ASQ - Aspring for Quality</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:08:22 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/vi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Asset Management</title>
      <link>/vi/whatwedo/am/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:08:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/whatwedo/am/</guid>
      <description>Asset Management is the optimal allocation of the scarce budget between the new arrangement of asset and rehabilitation, maintenance of the existing assets to maximize the value of the stock of assets and to realize the maximum outcomes for the stakeholders.
 We are capable of providing asset management services for various types of engineering and infrastructure systems such as water and waste water utilities (Water Treatment Plants, Pump Stations, and Pipeline), mechanical and electrical assets of industrial plants, bridge and pavement systems, and building assets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TDD cho mục đích mua bán và sát nhập (M&amp;A)</title>
      <link>/vi/whatwedo/tdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:08:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/whatwedo/tdd/</guid>
      <description>We provide Technical Due Diligence (TDD) services that involve a process of systematic review, analysis, and discovery of the conditions of assets from various viewpoints such as architectural, constructional, structural, MEP, fire safety and external façade checking.
The TDD services also consists of a review and analysis of cost estimation for short, medium, or long-term preventive intervention program. We utilize experience and knowledge of asset management in the context of TDD to provide optimal set of advices regarding future investment on the assets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction Industry Marketing</title>
      <link>/vi/whatwedo/constructionmarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:08:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/whatwedo/constructionmarket/</guid>
      <description>We combine market analysis techniques with knowledge and experience in econometrics, operations research, statistics, and engineering to provide an advantageous approach toward determination of optimal capital investment strategies on acquisition of existing properties or development of new properties taking into consideration of local settings and global trends. Our rich historical database on cost and price of assets, materials, and labor in construction and infrastructure sectors enables to perform various types of quantitative analysis, comparative study, and econometrical modelling to capture the equilibrium of price and market behaviors as well as influencing factors on specific properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Solutions and Analytics</title>
      <link>/vi/whatwedo/datascience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:08:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/whatwedo/datascience/</guid>
      <description>Time Series Data and Panel Data of Operations of Building and Engineering Systems such as a Water Treatment Plant, a Power Station, or a Pump Station, if being recorded and analyzed appropriately, will give engineers and managers a window of insightful pictures on
 Efficiency Reliability and Stability Correlation of variables Bottlenecks Risk factors and impacts  By understanding those, optimal decisions can be made. The tasks on data solutions and analytics can also be linked to Asset Management and Auditing tasks using the power of statistical correlation and prediction capacity, which could potentially save significant cost for asset&#39;s owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weibull Analysis - An example</title>
      <link>/vi/apps/weibulllcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 11:08:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/apps/weibulllcc/</guid>
      <description>Determination of Optimal Intervention Strategy for Pumps based on Weibull Analysis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>/vi/whatwedo/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/whatwedo/training/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building and Plant Audits</title>
      <link>/vi/business/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/business/audit/</guid>
      <description>We conduct inspection and testing for buildings and engineering systems to capture assets reliability &amp;amp; efficiency and compliance to applied standards</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cơ hội cho thị trường bất động sản công nghiệp thời Covid-19?</title>
      <link>/vi/blogs/vlog01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/blogs/vlog01/</guid>
      <description>Theo dự báo, nhu cầu thuê đất ở các khu công nghiệp được dự báo tiếp tục tăng trong năm 2020, bởi vốn đầu tư nước ngoài vào Việt Nam đang tăng mạnh, trước làn sóng di chuyển các cơ sở sản xuất từ Trung Quốc sang các nước Đông Nam Á.
 Mới đây, ông Troy Griffiths - Phó Tổng giám đốc Savills Việt Nam cho rằng Việt Nam là quốc gia đầu tiên công bố hết dịch SARS năm 2003 và sẽ tiếp tục thành công trong việc ngăn chặn dịch bệnh lần này.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Solutions and Analytics</title>
      <link>/vi/business/datasolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/business/datasolutions/</guid>
      <description>Using time series and panel dataset on engineering&#39;s parameters and variables of system, we can detect trends, establish correlation, and perform inference analysis that will support Clients on arriving at optimal business solutions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Monitoring</title>
      <link>/vi/business/digitalmornitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/business/digitalmornitoring/</guid>
      <description>Utilizing digital platform and frontier development on monitoring technique for engineering systems such as the use of drone for carrying out inspections on road sections, bridges, and other engineering systems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Impact Assessment</title>
      <link>/vi/business/transportation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vi/business/transportation/</guid>
      <description>We conduct TIA for development project and help Clients to acquire regulatory permits. Our solutions encompases also workzone optimization on road network to minimize negative impacts</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>